[{"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Do you think the world is a more peaceful place now than it was when you first became Dalai Lama?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "The younger one.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Really.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, sometimes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Do you ever feel temptation when you see a woman?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Fine.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Your Holiness, how are you?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Everything good.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Everything good?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Last now, almost seven years annually.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Everything healthy?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I got checked, yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Do you like being that famous?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "I think it depends on one's own sort of matters of attitude towards this sort of -- some sort of popularity or some sort of good name.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Celebrity?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "So you like famous people who are famous because they have done something serious, scientific?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Do you feel the world is a more peaceful place now than it was when you first became Dalai Lama?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes, in principle, I support, of course.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Do you think that is good for the world that they do this?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I don't think generally politicians come from democratic country.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Do you think sometimes the politicians forget that?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Big change.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "What do you think of modern China and how it's changed in the time that you've been Dalai Lama?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Are you pleased when you hear that?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Did that offend you?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Actually, he sent once sort of representing, something -- envoy or something, sent to me, explained the reason.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Did you understand why he did that?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "You understood that?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "He inquired about Tibet.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Did he give you assurances that he is going to help you?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Does he share that vision?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "It seems - of course, it's extremely sad, very sad.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "What do you say to people who are thinking of doing the same thing and why are more people doing this now?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "That's obvious.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "And what do you think it is?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "I don't think, no, no.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "But that is a big problem, isn't it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Now, firstly, you see, they are -- they are sort of policies regarding their own people, now things, you see, there are indications, the seriousness -- see, these are indications they more moderate, more realistic thinking.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you believe that they are thinking the right way?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Certainly, 100 percent.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "If the censorship -- if the censorship goes and the reality comes out, there is more chance of a deal?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "After this break.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "America?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Of course, the greatest modern country and I think a country, because of its democracy, the freedom, freedom of thought, freedom of speech, I think a lot of innovation, you see develop in this country.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What does America mean to you?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What do you think of what has happened to America and how can it get itself back on track again?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "There is that, not only America, but also in Europe.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Is it a false dream, having a lot of money?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I think leaders have to act according to border sort of --", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Who are the most impressive world leaders you've ever met in your life who have that heart element in them, who understand it?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I think Nelson Mandela, I think what -- are one of the sort of quite impressive.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "I mean, which people that you've ever met have really impressed you?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "The younger one.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "As a human being.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Not as president of America.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "He couldn't --", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Yes, right.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Is that hard?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, sometimes see people.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Do you ever feel temptation when you see a woman?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Really.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "ORGAN: Do you ever drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Have you ever smoked a cigarette?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Ever taken a drug?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I don't know, I'm just asking.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Then, then -- wait, wait, wait.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Have you always been peaceful?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Then -- after my play, I return to my room, and there is the bottle.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Did you drink it?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Do you watch television?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Usually, like Discovery, and some sort of documentary film.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "What programs would you watch?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Did you ever watch entertainment programs?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "(Speaking in foreign language)", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "You never watched \"American Idol\"?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Do you know who Simon Cowell is?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Do you listen to music?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Really.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I have no interest.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "No music at all?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Do you ever watch movies?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I saw movie, also the peace and war.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "You've never seen a movie?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "War and Peace.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "War and Peace?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "And you've never seen one of his movies?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Is he irritated that you've never seen one of his movies?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Do you ever use a computer?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Do you ever send an e-mail?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Have you ever used a cell phone?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I can literally, immediately after my final examination, that was 1959.", "docId": "120525pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "If I could replay one moment for you, what would it be?", "qSentId": 580}]